Greg, welcome to uh Detroit and
congratulations.
>> Thank you, man. It's excited to be here.
>> Hey, obviously you have uh three-year
relationship with with Drew Petting. I
imagine that was part of the appeal of
of coming to Detroit. Can you maybe just
explain the relationship and and what
you've enjoyed about playing under Drew
these last three seasons?
>> Yeah, it's been a lot of fun. Um
obviously I spent uh three years with
Drew in Arizona. Um and we've grown a
relationship. Um and obviously he trusts
me. Um, and so just to have the
opportunity to team up with him again,
I'm excited.
>> When you are in an offense with a lot of
playmakers, which you know was the case
in Arizona with, uh, Marv and, um, you
know, you got tight ends at both spots
here. You know, how do you find your way
and find a role when there's, you know,
so many guys commanding the ball?
>> I think you just lean on what I do best
and it's just being myself. Um,
obviously in the NFL, opportunities come
and go, and it's about what you do with
your opportunities when they come. Um,
and I've done that up to this point in
my career. Um, but man, I'm about
winning. I'm about winning ball. It's
not about, um, if I had 10 catches, it's
about if the team won. So, I'm joining a
a great organization, a a great team,
um, a great locker room, and I'm excited
to be here.
>> Appreciate you, man.
Nolan.
>> Hey, Greg. Welcome uh to Detroit. I'm
just curious, you're a guy who can do a
lot of different things on the football
field. Is there a role or a skill that
you feel like you're uh you know, is
your strength relative to to other
receivers out there?
>> When you say out there, do you mean like
with the Lions or just
>> just in general? Like is there is there
something that you find like makes you
stand out amongst other receivers in the
league? Uh,
for me, I mean, obviously I'm I'm
probably one of the smaller guys in the
league, so my stature um when you cut on
the tape, I'm not a big guy, but I'm a
guy who um lights up. I'm a guy who um
is tough, a guy who's not afraid to
catch the ball and get hit. And I think
something that I pride myself on is
getting yak. Um once I get the ball in
my hands, I'm not just trying to get a
first down or a couple yards. I'm I'm
trying to go the distance. So, I think
that's what sets me apart.
>> Well, I want to preface this next one by
saying I'm 5'7, but as a as a smaller
guy out there, you know, what um how do
you feel like you developed toughness?
When did that come into your game? When
did that become a part of who you are on
the football field?
>> Just the things that I've been through,
man. Um coming into the NFL, being
undrafted,
um just not a lot of people really
believing in what I can do as a player.
And it it really started in high school.
it started. Um, I had eight eight
division one offers. Uh, I'm not sure if
you guys know my story, but not a lot of
people wanted me. So, um, just just just
being tough in that being having that
tough mindset. Um, and just taking it to
the football field. And I love the I
love the game of football, so it's it's
easy for me to play hard. It's easy for
me to um just play with passion because
I love it.
>> Awesome. Thanks. Welcome to Detroit.
Thank you, Will.
>> Hey, Greg. I guess just tell us a little
more about your story, uh, coming out of
high school. Which schools were you
considering and and why Wake Forest in
the end?
>> Yeah, so, uh, it really boiled down to,
uh, Wake Forest, Iowa State, and, uh,
Maryland offered me a week before
signing day. Um, and when teams do that,
I they some something happened, whether
they lost a guy or, um, you're just not
a top priority. and Wake Forest had been
pretty consistent the whole time and I
decided it was a good fit, man. I felt
like they were going to use me and
obviously um my career at Wake Forest
showed that um it was the right fit for
me. Um and man, I don't know, man. I I
just I love the game of football and I
decided to leave school early. Um I
played two years at Wake. got red
shirted my my freshman year and I played
two and I left early and a lot of people
told me that it was a bad decision and
um ultimately I went undrafted um and
this is this will be my sixth team um in
eight years um and it's been a journey
man but it's the reason why I'm still
here. I'm still standing today because I
love the game and I believe in myself
and that's what it comes down to
believing in yourself.
Then it looks like you've got tons of
experience as a return man in the NFL.
Kick returns, punt returns. Last year
seemed to be maybe your most efficient
as a return man on punts, a careerhigh
in yards per return. In that area
specifically as as a punt returner, what
do you feel like clicked for you last
year, if anything?
>> I would say my confidence. Um,
like I said, being going in year eight
in the NFL, man, it's it's about
confidence on the field, man. There's a
lot of guys who get out there and
they've been drafted early or they've
been predicted to play early. And
honestly, they didn't really believe in
themselves that, you know, I belong out
here on this field. But, um, I do I do
believe in myself. I truly do. Um, and
you can see that in my play, man. I take
chances. Um, I take risk. You got to
take risk as a punt returner, man. You
got 11 guys running full speed trying to
take your head off. So, um, I believe in
myself, man. And like I said before, I
love football, so um it's nothing for me
to go out there and play with passion
and energy.
>> I appreciate it, bro. Welcome to
Detroit.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Dave,
>> hey, uh, congrats, Greg. Uh, back to
that whole journey for a sec. I don't
know if there's anything else about your
childhood that you know is part of that
underdog story that you can share, but I
was curious after that journey and after
all those lean years you spent in the uh
the NFL bouncing between teams, what
does it mean to have been, you know,
have the career that you've had after
all these years now?
>> It means a lot, man. It means it means a
lot and I wouldn't be here without uh my
support system. My dad has been my
biggest fan. Um, and there were days
when I I didn't really believe in
myself. I know I just sat here and said
I believe in myself, but obviously in
every story there's there's times where
you doubt yourself. Um, and you need a
support system. You need somebody to to
push you, somebody that knows who you
really are. And he's been that for me.
Um, and so he's helped me, man. And, um,
it's it's gotten me to this point. Um,
along with prayer, my prayer life has
grown tremendously. Um, and just really
just growing in prayer and just
believing in myself.
>> Did you ever come close to giving it up?
>> Um, I would say in 2020, man, uh, after
I got cut from the Falcons, um, I talked
to my agent and he told me to take the
CFL route. And
at that moment, I was like, ah, like
it's going to be tough for me to go to
CFL and and work my way back in the NFL.
Um, but that was that was a point where
I was like, "Okay, maybe this is the
point where I need to transition." And
man, I I've been so blessed to still be
able to do this. I got a call maybe two
days before I was supposed to go to the
CFL about a try out with the Cardinals
and
I ended up making the team and I spent
five years in Arizona.
>> Yeah. And so like man, it's just like
when you when you feel like you want to
quit, don't quit. Just just keep
pushing. And
man, the breakthrough is a breakthrough.
>> Yeah. No, there's something divine about
that maybe, right? That happened two
days before. Um back to patching for a
quick sec. How big of a reason was that
why you came to Detroit? Was he why you
came to Detroit? Uh it was a big reason
obviously just the the comfortable
factor, the trust, um the success that
I've had with him being my OC, the three
years together. Um Drew is very smart.
He knows exactly how to get people the
ball. Um as well as uh Khalif Raymond
taking another job somewhere else. I
seen that the the spot was vacant. So um
man, Detroit fits who I am as a man. the
grit, the toughness, um the the getting
it out of the mud, the just that's me.
That's my whole story. And uh when I got
a call from Detroit that they were
interested, it was no better fit.
>> And then last thing for me, um just on
Drew, you know, we're sort of getting to
know him here and kind of what he does.
Can you speak to his creativity? Like
what what is uh you know, we're used to
seeing some of that in the offense here.
How creative do you think, you know,
Drew will be with what he can do with
all the weapons that you guys have?
Yeah, I would like Drew to speak on that
himself. I don't want to I don't want to
put too much on him, but um obviously
just a a mix of the run in the pass
game. Um and yeah, I don't I don't want
to overstep. You you know what I'm
saying? I don't want to overstep him.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. No problem. Congrats.
>> Thank you, Rich.
>> Hey, Greg. Uh I'm not sure if you guys
have any like um maybe offseason
workouts or interactions with each
other, but from afar, what have your
impressions been of Jared Goff? the the
type of quarterback that he is and how
do you think you fit with him?
>> Yeah, so I haven't I haven't uh met
Jared as of recently. Um in 2019 as a
rookie, I had a quick stint with the LA
Rams and he was a quarterback there. Um
but obviously I was a rookie. He was um
QB1, not really probably paying
attention to me, but uh I got to see how
he came to work every single day and uh
he was a pro about it. Um, and that's
one thing that I I I can say I honestly
learned from just being in the league so
long and bouncing around from teams,
just watching how guys come to work. Um,
and obviously Jared's had success in
this league um because he's been a pro.
So, um, I'm sure that'll continue.
>> Appreciate it. All right, back to Will.
>> Hey, do you still have the same agent
who encouraged you to go to the CFL back
in 2020?
>> No.
>> Not not a coincidence. I I I take it.
>> Obviously, we didn't see eye to eye.
>> Yeah. And then, hey, when the Lions
called you, who was it that that first
reached out to you, or was that through
your agent?
>> It was through my agent. Yeah.
>> Okay. Who' you first talk to from the
Lions during this during this process?
>> Um, obviously Petting.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
uh, I I want to say just petting. Yeah.
And then everything else was through my
agent. Yeah.
>> Right on. Appreciate it. Yes, sir.